http://www.en.mepra-online.de/IdeasBuffet.html

Home, Products, Company, HR Catalog online, References, Newsletter, Download, Contact, Ideas for, Breakfast, Room-Service, 
Restaurant, Bar-Wine, Buffet, Pizzeria, SPA, New Products
首页 产品 公司 在线目录 销售参考 新闻通讯 下载 联系我们  灵感 早餐 客房服务
餐厅 酒吧 自助餐 比萨店 会所 新品

Ideas for Buffet
为您的自助餐厅增添灵感

Chafing Dishes & Buffet products are subject to severe daily stress. This pays off particularly quality and experience.
火锅菜和自助食物每日有严格的要求，所以需要高质量的产品来应对。

In the international fine dining scene MEPRA products are the first choice. - The prevailing standard of quality, 
design and innovation is extremely demanding.
在精致的餐桌上，MEPRA将是您的首选。- 质量上乘、设计优美和创意无限，无疑是您的理想之选。


MEPRA will more than fulfill these high standards. We produce all products in own factories in northern Italy.
MEPRA满足您各种高端精致的要求。我们在意大利北部地区设有自己的生产加工工厂。

Here is a small selection of our range
以下是我们的部分产品。

Custom made
量身定做

You may get all shapes of our range covered with a coloured titanium surface of your choice. Don´t hesitate to come back to us 
with your possible requests.
您选择的所有中意的产品，其表面都附有一层彩色钛膜。赶快来MEPRA选择你喜欢的产品吧!


Also you may get all flatware in silverplated or golden version.
同时，您还可选择镀银或者镀金的刀叉和匙。


Click here to visit our @home Division
点击访问我们的家居系列产品

Careers, Exhibitions Fairs, Press, Links, Impressum
职业 展会 媒体 链接 版权说明