http://www.en.mepra.eu/New_Products.html

home, products, company, catalog online, where to buy, newsletter, download, contact, idears for, colourful life, bar-wine, baking pizza, serving&dining, outdoor, news products

New Products最新产品

ELICA

"ELICA" is the latest MEPRA design of cutlery. "ELICA" means translated into English as much as helical or spiral, and are thus consistent design language of this cutlery again: an essential design feature of this massive, 4mm cutlery is crafted from solid stainless steel, which runs through the entire handle all the parts. This look lends the cutlery an understated elegance and dynamism. Also offers this product with a soulful feel and balance that can be given an idea of figures.
"ELICA"是MEPRA最新的餐具设计系列."ELICA"意为螺旋旋转. 其显著的设计特点为, 仅为4mm厚度的餐具全部由坚固的不锈钢制作而成. 这款设计代表着无尚的优雅和活力,仿如意大利的艺术雕像一般, 为产品注入了灵魂和魅力

Of course, the 18/10 stainless steel cutlery is dishwasher safe and the toughest everyday use, thanks in Italian forging technology, in the demanding hotel and restaurant ideally suited. See all common accessories, from the fish knife and numerous additional items are also available on this model.
当然,此款18/10不锈钢餐具可用自动清洗机清洗,另外得益于意大利精良的锻造技术,该系列可供酒店和餐厅日常频繁使用. 从鱼叉到其他各种餐具配件,我们都可以制作成ELICA系列的各种样式.

The new MEPRA Collection....
MEPRA新系列...

ATENA

"ATENA" is the other new design of MEPRA cutlery. "Atena" is solid, edgy and factual. " - Looking at this new flatware you guessed the particular material thickness of 4 mm stainless steel, you can see the sophisticated feeling.
"ATENA"是MEPRA餐具的另一款新型设计.稳定坚固就是"ATENA"产品的特点-- 产品厚度仅为4mm,由不锈钢铸成. 
Of course, the 18/10 stainless steel cutlery is dishwasher safe and the toughest everyday use, thanks in Italian forging technology, in the demanding hotel and restaurant ideally suited. See all common accessories, from the fish knife and numerous additional items are also available on this model.
当然,此款18/10不锈钢餐具可用自动清洗机清洗,另外得益于意大利精良的锻造技术,该系列可供酒店和餐厅日常频繁使用. 从鱼叉到其他各种餐具配件,我们都可以制作成ATENA系列的各种样式.

ECO - CERAMIC  ECO-陶瓷
This is the new ECO CERAMIC collection, the new generation of non-stick cookware, worlds first from MEPRA, with body of thick stainless-steel in combination with EXCILON ?, the innovative white coating.  - Safer and more healthy because also of these features:
MEPRA世界首创的新一代不粘锅锅具,锅身为加入EXCILON材质的厚度不锈钢,并采用了创新的白底涂层工艺. 另外还具有更多健康安全的特点:
- Excellent non-stick, will not burn during cooking
   不粘锅, 烹饪过程中不会烧伤
- Physical hardness is high, excellent heat impact resistance, anti-rust and anti-abrasion
   良好的抗热,防锈,耐磨物理性能
- Easy to remove any residues when washing the pan
   锅身清洁方便彻底
Environment-Friendly: 环保
- It is a pollution free material and meets the VOC regulations 
  原材料为零污染原料,符合VOC相关条规
- There is no odour, and no air pollution
    无异味 无污浊
- It does not cause soil contamination
   材料不会导致土壤污染
- It is non-stick. Excellent acid, alkali resistance, solvent resistance. PFTE-Free, PFOA-Free
   良好的抗酸抗碱性 耐溶剂性 不含PFTE及PFDA
No harm产品安全健康: 
- It is not containing poisonous materials 
   不含任何有毒物质
- It is not containing any corrosive materials 
   不含任何腐蚀性物质
Availiable with ergonomic handles and glass-lids in 6 different trend-colours
该系列产品拥有人性化手柄设计,并搭配玻璃锅盖,共有6种不同的时尚颜色可供挑选

Click here to visit our Hotel & Restaurant Division

Exhibitions Fairs, Press, links, impressum