http://www.en.mepra-online.de/TitaniumFlatware.html

home, products, company, catalog online, where to buy, newsletter, download, contact, idears for, colourful life, bar-wine, 
baking pizza, serving&dining, outdoor, news products
首页 产品 公司 在线目录 哪里购买 新闻通讯 下载 联系我们 灵感 多姿生活 酒类 
比萨 服务&晚宴 户外 新品

Flatware, Flatware, Titanium Flatware, Fantasia Colours
餐具 餐具 钛餐具 绚丽色彩

Titanium Flatware
钛餐具

A new technology
全新技术

Mepra received for these cutlery models, manufactured by a new process technology,  covering the entire surface of the cutlery 
permanently with a colored titanium coating, extraordinary design awards.
The following color versions are possible:
Mepra 采用全新加工技术，餐具表面可附着一层永久性彩色钛膜，设计新颖，荣获多次设计大奖。


Black, matt gold, shiny gold, bronze color.
黑色  亚光金 亮金色 铜色

The surface of these models is 4 times as hard as stainless steel, so it is possible to provide even the blade of the knife 
get the same color.
有色彩表面的餐具非常坚固耐用，是普通不锈钢的4倍，因此即使在刀刃上也同样可采用该项技术。


All these shapes resist the toughest handling, of course they are also dishwasher safe.
所有的餐具可满足您各种使用方法，同样也适用于洗碗机。


Due Oro Nero, Linea Oro Ice, Due Bronzo, Linea Bronzo, Due Oro Nero, Linea Oro Nero, Due Oro Ice, Linea Oro Ice

Custom made
量身定制

You may get all shapes of our range covered with a coloured titanium surface of your choice. Don´t hesitate to come back to us 
with your possible requests.
您选择的所有中意产品，其表面都附有一层彩色钛膜。赶快来MEPRA选择你喜欢的产品吧！

Also you may get all flatware in silverplated or golden version
此外，MEPRA所有产品有镀银或镀金系列供您选择。

Click here to visit our Hotel & Restaurant Division
点击访问我们的酒店 & 餐厅部门

Exhibitions Fairs, Press, links, impressum
展会 媒体 链接 版本说明