http://www.en.mepra.eu/DueOroIce.html

home, products, company, catalog online, where to buy, newsletter, download, contact, idears for, colourful life, bar-wine, baking pizza, serving&dining, outdoor, news products

Due Oro Ice

A new technology
新型技术
Mepra manufactured those products by a new process technology, covering the entire surface of the cutlery permanently with a colored titanium coating the worlds first. The surface of these models is 4 times as hard as stainless steel. All these shapes resist the toughest handling, of course they are also dishwasher safe.
MEPRA通过世界首创的新型加工技术,可为餐具的各个层面永久添加彩色钛涂层. 加工后餐具表面的坚硬程度相当于不锈钢的4倍.
所有的该系列产品均非常耐用坚固, 当然,可以用自动清洁机清洁
This colour looks exactly like gold, but it′s as many times more resistable.
颜色非常类似与金色,十分耐用坚固

Click here to visit our Hotel & Restaurant Division

Exhibitions Fairs, Press, links, impressum