http://www.en.mepra.eu/Polycarbonate.html

home, products, company, catalog online, where to buy, newsletter, download, contact, idears for, colourful life, bar-wine, baking pizza, serving&dining, outdoor, news products

SPA Wellness SPA健康中心
Outdoor 户外
Polycarbonate 聚碳酸酯PC

The stunning and unbreakable 'Polycarbonate' range is produced using the highest quality raw ingredients available in the world. The patented process results in a superb 'glass' look and feel. The range comes in a fantastic array of retro colours and the items available will suit all occasions. As the Mepra Polycarbonate ware is unbreakable, it is perfect for pool areas, outdoors, bars & nightclubs, Aged Care Centre, Hospitals and more. Look for the Mepra Polycarbonate Party Plate that holds a champagne or wine glass – great for stand up function or parties around the pool.
抢眼外观和坚不可摧构成了"PC聚碳酸酯"系列的主要特征.该系列产品采用世界上最优质的原材料制作而成, 通过专利加工工艺,产品外观酷似玻璃. 产品含括各种时尚的梦幻色彩,可在任何场合搭配使用. 由于其不易破碎的特性, 产品非常适合在泳池,户外,酒吧&俱乐部,老年人护理中心,医院等场合使用. 可放置醉人香槟和迷人酒杯的MEPRA 聚碳酸酯PC系列晚会托盘, 是各种海滩泳池party的绝佳选择 
Here is a small selection of our range, for further details look at ?Ideas SPA“
部分产品展示. 更多内容请参阅"海滩创意"

Click here to visit our Hotel & Restaurant Division

Exhibitions Fairs, Press, links, impressum