http://www.en.mepra.eu/PotsPans.html

home, products, company, catalog online, where to buy, newsletter, download, contact, idears for, colourful life, bar-wine, baking pizza, serving&dining, outdoor, news products

Pots & Pans锅类
Attiva

These 3-layer aluinox 18/10 pots by Mepra have an aluminum core throughout that evenly distributes heat for uniform cooking with little water and fat resulting in a more wholesome and flavorful food. 
由3层铝制材料制成的18/10锅具,拥有强大的铝制导热中心,可在烹饪过程中均匀分布热量,即便是少量水和肉类烹饪,也能制作出更加健康可口的佳肴
Other benefits: greater control over cooking temperature, energy-saving cooking, useful lip allows accurate pouring, suitable for all types of hobs, especially induction hobs, dishwasher safe.
其他特点: 更好的温度控制功能; 热量储存烹饪;人性化边缘设计; 适合一切烹饪设备,特别是电磁炉;安全机洗
Toscana

Toscana pots and pans by Mepra are made of an aluminum core sandwiched between and inside layer of 18/10 stainless steel and copper outside, guaranteeing excellent heat conducting properties. 

Other benefits: greater control over cooking temperatures, allows gentle cooking with little water and fat for more wholesome and flavorful food, dishwasher safe, suitable for all types of hobs except induction hobs.
Toscana系列锅具内层为18/10不锈钢材料,外层为铜,中间加入铝制隔层,造就了良好的锅身导热性

其他特点:良好的温度控制功能;可文火烹饪少量食物,更健康可口;安全机洗; 适合除电磁炉外的任意烹饪设备

?1950“

?1950“ items are designed as a reference to the style of the 50`s. A heavy body of 18/10 stainless steel  guarantees an excellent heat conducting property. 
?1950“系列根据50年代的产品样式设计. 18/10不锈钢的重量锅身保证了该系列产品的良好加热性能

Other benefits: greater control over cooking temperatures, allows gentle cooking with little water and fat for more wholesome and flavorful food, dishwasher safe, suitable for all types of hobs except induction hobs.
其他特点: 良好的温度控制功能;可文火烹饪少量食物,更健康可口;安全机洗; 适合除电磁炉外的任意烹饪设备
Energia

Energia line by Mepra offers unique and practical pots with graduated measurements inside that make cooking easier. The dutch pot can be used on any type of hob or in the oven. Dishwasher and fridge safe.
Energia 系列产品拥有独特的设计和实用的功能,内部刻有测量刻度,使得烹饪更加简易精准. 该系列锅具可在任意烹饪设备上使用,甚至也可在烤箱中使用. 可安全使用清洁机和冰箱

Eco-Ceramic

Here is the new generation of non-stick cookware, worlds first from MEPRA, with body of thick stainless-steel in combination with EXCILON ?, the innovative white coating. 
MEPRA世界首创的新一代不粘锅锅具,锅身为加入EXCILON的厚度不锈钢,创新的白底漆工艺. 
Safer and more healthy because also of these features:
另外还具有更多健康安全的特点:
Excellent non-stick, will not burn during cooking.
   不粘锅, 烹饪过程中不会烧伤
Physical hardness is high, excellent heat impact resistance, anti-rust and anti-abrasion.
   良好的抗热,防锈,耐磨物理性能
Easy to remove any residues when washing the pan.
   锅身清洁方便彻底
Environment-Friendly: 
环保
- It is a pollution free material and meets the VOC regulations 
  原材料为零污染原料,符合VOC相关条规
- There is no odour, and no air pollution
    无异味 无污浊
- It does not cause soil contamination
   材料不会导致土壤污染
- It is non-stick. Excellent acid, alkali resistance, solvent resistance. PFTE-Free, PFOA-Free
   良好的抗酸抗碱性 耐溶剂性 不含PFTE及PFDA
   
No harm产品无危害: 
- It is not containing poisonous materials 
   不含任何有毒物质
- It is not containing any corrosive materials 
   不含任何腐蚀性物质

Frying pans diameter 20-24-28cm - Wok-Pan  28cm with lid 
煎锅尺寸20-24-28cm,炒锅  28cm含锅盖
availiable with ergonomic handles and glass-lids in 6 different trend-colours.
该系列产品拥有人性化手柄设计,并搭配玻璃锅盖,共有6种不同的时尚颜色可供挑选
Click here to visit our Hotel & Restaurant Division

Exhibitions Fairs, Press, links, impressum