http://www.en.mepra.eu/TitaniumFlatware.html

home, products, company, catalog online, where to buy, newsletter, download, contact, idears for, colourful life, bar-wine, baking pizza, serving&dining, outdoor, news products

Flatware, Flatware, Titanium Flatware, Fantasia Colours

Titanium Flatware钛层餐具

A new technology
新型技术

Mepra received for these cutlery models, manufactured by a new process technology,  covering the entire surface of the cutlery permanently with a colored titanium coating, extraordinary design awards.
该系列产品通过新型技术加工,整个餐具表面均可永久添加多彩钛涂层. MEPRA因为该项新型技术产品在世界上率获殊荣.
The following color versions are possible:
可供选择的颜色有:
Black, matt gold, shiny gold, bronze color.
黑色,哑金色,亮金色,赤铜色
The surface of these models is 4 times as hard as stainless steel, so it is possible to provide even the blade of the knife get the same color.
这类产品的表面比不锈钢坚硬四倍,甚至连刀刃上也可以涂上相同颜色
All these shapes resist the toughest handling, of course they are also dishwasher safe.
该系列所有产品均非常耐用坚固, 当然,可以用自动清洁机清洁
Due Oro Nero, Linea Oro Ice, Due Bronzo, Linea Bronzo, Due Oro Nero, Linea Oro Nero, Due Oro Ice, Linea Oro Ice

Custom made
定制产品
You may get all shapes of our range covered with a coloured titanium surface of your choice. Don′t hesitate to come back to us with your possible requests.
该系列的各式产品均可选择不同颜色的钛表涂层. 如有任何要求,请随时联系我们
Also you may get all flatware in silverplated or golden version
而且您还可以选择定制成银制或金制涂层
Click here to visit our Hotel & Restaurant Division

Exhibitions Fairs, Press, links, impressum