http://www.en.mepra-online.de/DueOroIce.html

home, products, company, catalog online, where to buy, newsletter, download, contact, idears for, colourful life, bar-wine, 
baking pizza, serving&dining, outdoor, news products
首页 产品 公司 在线目录 哪里购买 新闻通讯 下载 联系我们 灵感 多姿生活 酒类 
比萨 服务&晚宴 户外 新品

Due Oro Ice
A new technology
全新技术

Mepra manufactured those products by a new process technology, covering the entire surface of the cutlery permanently 
with a colored titanium coating the worlds first. The surface of these models is 4 times as hard as stainless steel. 
All these shapes resist the toughest handling, of course they are also dishwasher safe.
Mepra全球首次采用全新技术为产品表面添加彩色钛金涂层，且永久保留。该涂层的硬度是普通不锈钢的4倍，因此，刀刃也同样
采用该技术添加彩色涂层。

This colour looks exactly like gold, but it´s as many times more resistable.
该颜色与金色非常相近，但是却非常坚固耐用。

Click here to visit our Hotel & Restaurant Division
点击此处访问我们的酒店&餐厅部门

Exhibitions Fairs, Press, links, impressum
展会 媒体 链接 版权说明
