http://www.en.mepra-online.de/Polycarbonate.html

home, products, company, catalog online, where to buy, newsletter, download, contact, idears for, colourful life, bar-wine, 
baking pizza, serving&dining, outdoor, news products
首页 产品 公司 在线目录 哪里购买 新闻通讯 下载 联系我们 灵感 多姿生活 酒类 
比萨 服务&晚宴 户外 新品

SPA Wellness
Outdoor
Polycarbonate
SPA 舒适系列
户外
聚碳酸酯

The stunning and unbreakable 'Polycarbonate' range is produced using the highest quality raw ingredients available in the world. 
The patented process results in a superb 'glass' look and feel. The range comes in a fantastic array of retro colours 
and the items available will suit all occasions. As the Mepra Polycarbonate ware is unbreakable, it is perfect for pool areas, 
outdoors, bars & nightclubs, Aged Care Centre, Hospitals and more. Look for the Mepra Polycarbonate Party Plate that holds a 
champagne or wine glass – great for stand up function or parties around the pool.
绚丽且不易碎的“聚碳酸酯”系列采用可能世界各地取得的优质原材料。该项获得专利的“聚碳酸酯”加工技术，使该系列产品同样具有“玻璃”
质感。该系列品种繁多，充满复古色彩，适用于各种场所。Mepra聚碳酸酯餐具不易破碎，非常适合用于游泳场所，户外，酒吧&夜店，老年护理中心，
医院及其他场所。快来体验Mepra 聚碳酸酯系列，在party上端上一杯香槟或白酒——您会发觉该李烈非常适合于站立聚会或者泳池边酒会。


Here is a small selection of our range, for further details look at „Ideas SPA“
以下是我们的部分产品，要了解跟多产品信息，请点击“会所灵感”

Click here to visit our Hotel & Restaurant Division
点击此处访问我们的酒店&餐厅系列

Exhibitions Fairs, Press, links, impressum
展会 媒体 链接 版本说明