http://www.en.mepra-online.de/PotsPans.html

home, products, company, catalog online, where to buy, newsletter, download, contact, idears for, colourful life, bar-wine, 
baking pizza, serving&dining, outdoor, news products
首页 产品 公司 在线目录 哪里购买 新闻通讯 下载 联系我们 灵感 多姿生活 酒类 
比萨 服务&晚宴 户外 新品

Pots & Pans
Attiva
锅 & 碟
Attiva系列锅具

These 3-layer aluinox 18/10 pots by Mepra have an aluminum core throughout that evenly distributes heat for uniform cooking with 
little water and fat resulting in a more wholesome and flavorful food. 
Mepra 3层aluinox 18/10 锅通体为铝芯，均匀导热，可在少量水和油的条件下烹饪，食物既健康又美味。

Other benefits: greater control over cooking temperature, energy-saving cooking, useful lip allows accurate pouring, suitable for 
all types of hobs, especially induction hobs, dishwasher safe.

其他优点： 烹饪温度可完全掌控；节能；锅口边缘设计可精准倾倒；锅体设计设用于所有炉盘，特别是嵌入式炉盘；适用于洗碗机。

Toscana
Toscana系列锅具

Toscana pots and pans by Mepra are made of an aluminum core sandwiched between and inside layer of 18/10 stainless steel and 
copper outside, guaranteeing excellent heat conducting properties. 
Toscana系列锅具和碟为铝制锅芯，内部为18/10不锈钢，外部由铜包裹，确保最佳热传导性能。

Other benefits: greater control over cooking temperatures, allows gentle cooking with little water and fat for more wholesome 
and flavorful food, dishwasher safe, suitable for all types of hobs except induction hobs.
其他优点：烹饪温度可完全掌控，在少许水和油的条件下既可烹饪健康美味的食物；适用于洗碗机；除嵌入式炉盘外，适用于其他所有炉盘。

„1950“
„1950“系列锅具

„1950“ items are designed as a reference to the style of the 50`s. A heavy body of 18/10 stainless steel  guarantees an 
excellent heat conducting property. 
„1950“系列锅具设计参考50年代设计风格，锅体为18/10不锈钢，厚重的锅体确保良好的导热性能。

Other benefits: greater control over cooking temperatures, allows gentle cooking with little water and fat for more wholesome 
and flavorful food, dishwasher safe, suitable for all types of hobs except induction hobs.
其他优点： 烹饪温度可完全掌控；在少许水和油的条件下既可烹饪健康美味的食物；适用于洗碗机；除嵌入式炉盘外，适用于其他所有炉盘。

Energia
Energia 锅具系列

Energia line by Mepra offers unique and practical pots with graduated measurements inside that make cooking easier. The dutch pot 
can be used on any type of hob or in the oven. Dishwasher and fridge safe.
MEPRA Enrigia系列为您打造独特且操作简洁的锅具，内部配有温度指示，更易于操作。这款锅具可适用于所有炉盘及烤箱；适用于洗碗机和冰箱。

Eco-Ceramic
Eco-Ceramic系列

Here is the new generation of non-stick cookware, worlds first from MEPRA, with body of thick stainless-steel in combination with 
EXCILON ®, the innovative white coating. 
Eco-Ceramic为不沾锅系列，为MEPRA全球首次研发生产，不锈钢材质结合EXCILON ®的创新白色涂层技术。

Safer and more healthy because also of these features:
使用更加安全，该系列其他特性有：

Excellent non-stick, will not burn during cooking.
绝佳的不沾锅特性，烹饪时避免食物烧焦。

Physical hardness is high, excellent heat impact resistance, anti-rust and anti-abrasion.
锅体坚固，具良好的热冲击阻力，防锈，耐磨损。

Easy to remove any residues when washing the pan.
清洗时，残渣极易冲洗。

Environment-Friendly: 
- is a pollution free material and meets the VOC regulations. 
here is no odour, and no air pollution. 
- does not cause soil contamination. 
- is non-stick. Excellent acid, alkali resistance, solvent resistance. PFTE-Free, PFOA-Free.
环保：
- 无污染材质，且达到VOC标准。
无气味，对空气无污染。
- 堆土地无污染。
- 不粘锅；良好的抗酸、碱性，抗溶性。不含PFTE，不含PFOA。


No harm: 
- is not containing poisonous materials. 
- is not containing any corrosive materials. 

无毒害
- 不含有毒害材料。
- 不含腐蚀性材料。

Frying pans diameter 20-24-28cm - Wok-Pan  28cm with lid 
煎锅直径为20-24cm - 炒锅直径为28cm，带锅盖。

availiable with ergonomic handles and glass-lids in 6 different trend-colours.
构造符合人体工程学，带玻璃锅盖并有6种颜色可供选择。

Click here to visit our Hotel & Restaurant Division
点击此处访问我们的酒店&餐厅部门

Exhibitions Fairs, Press, links, impressum
展会 媒体 链接 版本说明