http://www.en.mepra-online.de/Winecoolers.html

home, products, company, catalog online, where to buy, newsletter, download, contact, idears for, colourful life, bar-wine, 
baking pizza, serving&dining, outdoor, news products
首页 产品 公司 在线目录 哪里购买 新闻通讯 下载 联系我们 灵感 多姿生活 酒类 
比萨 服务&晚宴 户外 新品

Winecoolers

MEPRA offers a huge selection of products for bar & wine, numerous varieties of wine and sparkling wine coolers, ice buckets, 
trays, glasses, stirrers, shakers, trolleys, and much more ...
MEPRA 为您提供种类齐全的酒具，式样丰富，各种冷却器、冰桶、托盘、玻璃杯、搅拌棒、推车、混合器及其他更多产品选择。

Custom made
量身定做

You may get all shapes of our range covered with a coloured titanium surface of your choice. Don´t hesitate to come back to 
us with your possible requests.
您选择的所有中意产品，其表面都附有一层彩色钛膜。赶快来MEPRA选择你喜欢的产品吧！

Also you may get all flatware in silverplated or golden version.
同时，您还可选择镀银或者镀金的刀叉和匙。

Here is a small selection of our range
以下是我们的部分产品。

Custom made
量身定做

You may get all shapes of our range covered with a coloured titanium surface of your choice. Don´t hesitate to come back to 
us with your possible requests.
MEPRA 为您提供种类齐全的酒具，式样丰富，各种冷却器、冰桶、托盘、玻璃杯、搅拌棒、推车、混合器及其他更多产品选择。

Also you may get all flatware in silverplated or golden version.
同时，您还可选择镀银或者镀金的刀叉和匙。

Click here to visit our Hotel & Restaurant Division
点击访问我们的酒店&餐厅部门

Exhibitions Fairs, Press, links, impressum
展会 媒体 链接 版本说明