http://www.en.mepra-online.de/IdeasRoomService.html

Home, Products, Company, HR Catalog online, References, Newsletter, Download, Contact, Ideas for, Breakfast, Room-Service, 
Restaurant, Bar-Wine, Buffet, Pizzeria, SPA, New Products
首页 产品 公司 在线目录 销售参考 新闻通讯 下载 联系我们  灵感 早餐 客房服务
餐厅 酒吧 自助餐 比萨店 会所 新品

Ideas for Room-Service
为您的客房服务增添灵感

The MEPRA room service concept includes not only the right trolleys in different variants, but also optionally cloches / plates 
with a heat element. The cloches can be customized at the factory to your specific plate size. By this your plates fit perfectly 
to the cloches.
MEPRA客房服务不仅包括用于不同场所的餐厅推车，还有可供选择的保温型钟形盖/盘，同时，MEPRA工厂还将根据所需，为您特别定制，使您的餐盘
完全符合钟形盖构造。

All other possible accessories that you need for this personal service, of course  we offer in our program.
MEPRA还将为您提供其他个性服务所需配件。

Here is a small selection of our range
以下是我们的部分产品。

Custom made
量身定制

You may get all shapes of our range covered with a coloured titanium surface of your choice. Don´t hesitate to come back to us 
with your possible requests.
您选择的所有中意产品，其表面都附有一层彩色钛膜。赶快来MEPRA选择你喜欢的产品吧

Also you may get all flatware in silverplated or golden version.
同时，您还可选择镀银或者镀金的刀叉和匙。

Click here to visit our @home Division
点击访问我们的家居部门

Career, Exhibitions Fairs, Press, links, impressum
职业 展会 媒体 链接 版权说明