http://www.en.mepra-online.de/IdeasBarWine.html

Home, Products, Company, HR Catalog online, References, Newsletter, Download, Contact, Ideas for, Breakfast, Room-Service, 
Restaurant, Bar-Wine, Buffet, Pizzeria, SPA, New Products
首页 产品 公司 在线目录 销售参考 新闻通讯 下载 联系我们  灵感 早餐 客房服务
餐厅 酒吧 自助餐 比萨店 会所 新品

Ideas for Bar & Wine

MEPRA offers a huge selection of products for bar & wine, numerous varieties of wine and sparkling wine coolers, ice buckets, 
trays, glasses, stirrers, shakers, trolleys, and much more ...
为您的酒吧增添灵感
MEPRA为您提供酒吧用所有产品，各种酒器及冷酒器，冰桶，托盘，玻璃杯，搅拌棒，混合器，手推车及更多产品


Here is a small selection of our range
以下我我们的部分产品

Custom made
量身定制

You may get all shapes of our range covered with a coloured titanium surface of your choice. Don´t hesitate to come back to us 
with your possible requests.
您选择的所有中意的产品，其表面都附有一层彩色钛膜。赶快来MEPRA选择你喜欢的产品吧!


Also you may get all flatware in silverplated or golden version.
同时，您还可选择镀银或者镀金的刀叉和匙。

Click here to visit our @home Division
点击访问我们的家居部门

Career, Exhibitions Fairs, Press, links, impressum
职业 展会 媒体 链接 版权说明