http://www.en.mepra-online.de/IdeasRestaurant.html

Home, Products, Company, HR Catalog online, References, Newsletter, Download, Contact, Ideas for, Breakfast, Room-Service, 
Restaurant, Bar-Wine, Buffet, Pizzeria, SPA, New Products
首页 产品 公司 在线目录 销售参考 新闻通讯 下载 联系我们  灵感 早餐 客房服务
餐厅 酒吧 自助餐 比萨店 会所 新品

Ideas for Restaurant
In the international fine dining scene MEPRA products are the first choice. - The prevailing standard of quality, 
design and innovation is extremely demanding.

为您的餐厅增添灵感
在精致的餐桌上，MEPRA将是您的首选。- 质量上乘、设计优美和创意无限，无疑是您的理想之选。

MEPRA will more than fulfill these high standards. We produce  all products in own factories in northern Italy.
MEPRA满足您各种高端精致的要求。我们在意大利北部地区设有自己的生产加工工厂。

By using our equipment menus and banquets lead customers to a distinctive and lasting experience. Profit from our 
knowledge and competition!
选择使用MEPRA产品招待客人或安排盛宴将为您带来与众不同的感受，并且将会一直延续下去。我们将会用我们的知识及竞争优势来换取您的青睐。

Here is a small selection of our range
以下是我们的部分产品。

Custom made
量身定做

You may get all shapes of our range covered with a coloured titanium surface of your choice. Don´t hesitate to come back to us 
with your possible requests.
您选择的所有中意产品，其表面都附有一层彩色钛膜。赶快来MEPRA选择你喜欢的产品吧！

Also you may get all flatware in silverplated or golden version.
同时，您还可选择镀银或者镀金的刀叉和匙。


Click here to visit our @home Division
点击访问我们的家居部门

Career, Exhibitions Fairs, Press, links, impressum
职业 展会 媒体 链接 版权说明